<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Climate Change and Extreme Weather Events on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/global-climate-change-and-extreme-weather-events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Global Climate Change and Extreme Weather Events on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/global-climate-change-and-extreme-weather-events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Merlin&#39;s Beard! Weather Weirder Than a Weasley Experiment!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/merlins-beard-weather-weirder-than-a-weasley-exper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/merlins-beard-weather-weirder-than-a-weasley-exper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By Barnaby Bumble, Daily Prophet Meteorological Correspondent&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Magic is scrambling to understand increasingly erratic weather patterns plaguing the wizarding world. Experts are blaming, well, mostly everyone, and pointing fingers faster than a Niffler at Gringotts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re seeing blizzards in July,&amp;rdquo; sputtered a frazzled Professor Flitwick, who nearly lost his voice trying to shout over a rogue hailstorm hammering Hogwarts during our interview. &amp;ldquo;July! And the Great Lake… it’s practically evaporated! Except when it’s spontaneously turning into treacle! Honestly, the mermaids are threatening to unionize!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wizengamot Debates Dramatic Shifts in Weather: Is Magic to Blame?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/wizengamot-debates-dramatic-shifts-in-weather-is-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/wizengamot-debates-dramatic-shifts-in-weather-is-m/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Wizengamot was in uproar yesterday as Minister for Magic Kingsley Shacklebolt addressed the escalating concerns surrounding increasingly erratic and extreme weather patterns across the British Isles and beyond. Reports are flooding in from all corners of the wizarding world: torrential Acid Pops deluges in Hogsmeade, spontaneously combusting cauldrons in Knockturn Alley, and even a rogue blizzard of self-folding laundry terrorising Little Whinging.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We are not taking these matters lightly,&amp;rdquo; Minister Shacklebolt assured the assembled members, though his claim was somewhat undermined by the faint smell of burnt toast emanating from his robes (sources say a particularly aggressive batch of self-stirring porridge was to blame). &amp;ldquo;The Department of Magical Catastrophes is working tirelessly to identify the cause of these… &lt;em&gt;irregularities&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
