<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Economic Inequality and Social Justice Movements on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/economic-inequality-and-social-justice-movements/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Economic Inequality and Social Justice Movements on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/economic-inequality-and-social-justice-movements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gringotts Gorbles: A Goblin&#39;s Lament on Wage Inequality and the SPEW Revival</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/features/gringotts-gorbles-a-goblins-lament-on-wage-inequal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/features/gringotts-gorbles-a-goblins-lament-on-wage-inequal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By Bathilda Bagshot (Granddaughter of &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; Bathilda Bagshot)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is the wizarding world truly equal? While we all enjoy the benefits of magic – instant cleaning, self-stirring cauldrons, and the occasional levitation of Dudley Dursley&amp;rsquo;s pudding – a chasm of inequality yawns beneath our polished wands. We&amp;rsquo;re not talking about pure-blood snobbery (though Merlin knows that&amp;rsquo;s still a problem). We&amp;rsquo;re talking about cold, hard Galleons.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Take, for instance, our esteemed goblin colleagues at Gringotts. While the Ministry enjoys bottomless coffers (likely refilled with questionable accounting spells), rumours swirl of goblins struggling to afford sufficient polishing paste for their impressively sharp teeth. Grunt Gringotts employee, Grilk (who wished to remain anonymous for fear of being turned into a particularly nasty paperweight), whispered, &amp;ldquo;We guard the gold, but we see very little of it ourselves! The dragons get better dental!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
