<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Public Health Crises and Disease Outbreaks on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/public-health-crises-and-disease-outbreaks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Public Health Crises and Disease Outbreaks on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/public-health-crises-and-disease-outbreaks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Sprout&#39;s Super Sniffles Sweep Hogwarts! Mandrakes Blamed!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/breaking-news/breaking-sprouts-super-sniffles-sweep-hogwarts-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/breaking-news/breaking-sprouts-super-sniffles-sweep-hogwarts-man/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry is currently grappling with a sudden outbreak of what is being dubbed &amp;lsquo;Sprout&amp;rsquo;s Super Sniffles,&amp;rsquo; a particularly virulent form of magical influenza. Symptoms include excessive sneezing (often resulting in accidental conjuration of small household objects), a persistent cough that sounds suspiciously like mandrake screams (without the fatal petrification, thankfully), and an inexplicable craving for pumpkin pasties.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Professor Pomona Sprout, Head of Herbology, is under immediate suspicion. Initial investigations point towards a rogue batch of Mandrakes, possibly cross-bred with something equally unpleasant (the details are still hazy and involve Ernie Macmillan&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate proximity to a Whomping Willow during harvesting). Professor Sprout, when questioned, was reportedly mortified and muttered something about &amp;rsquo;those blasted seedlings&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;investing in earmuffs with better Silencing Charms.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
