<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quidditch on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/quidditch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quidditch on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/quidditch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gringotts Goblin Gripes: Knuts in Crisis as Quidditch Prices Soar!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/quidditch/gringotts-goblin-gripes-knuts-in-crisis-as-quiddit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/quidditch/gringotts-goblin-gripes-knuts-in-crisis-as-quiddit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Diagon Alley is abuzz with more than just Butterbeer froth this week, as whispers of a brewing economic crisis are causing concern amongst Quidditch enthusiasts and players alike. Gringotts goblins, notoriously tight-lipped, are reportedly grappling with a volatile Knut-to-Sickle exchange rate, leading to widespread inflation across the Quidditch supply chain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The price of quality Firebolts has skyrocketed, with even Nimbus 2000s fetching Galleons that would make a Weasley blush. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s outrageous!&amp;rdquo; exclaimed Barnaby Proudfoot, captain of the Chudley Cannons. &amp;ldquo;I remember when a decent set of Bludger-batting gloves cost a few Sickles. Now? Forget about it! We&amp;rsquo;re resorting to self-repair charms and second-hand shops just to keep the team equipped!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wizengamot Debates Broomstick Emissions: Can Quidditch Survive Atmospheric Unbalancing?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/quidditch/wizengamot-debates-broomstick-emissions-can-quiddi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/quidditch/wizengamot-debates-broomstick-emissions-can-quiddi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By Elara Finch-Fletchley, Quidditch Correspondent&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whispers have grown to shouts in the stands, and even the Wizengamot is taking notice: the increasingly erratic weather during Quidditch matches isn&amp;rsquo;t just bad luck. A growing consensus amongst magical meteorologists, spearheaded by Professor Aurora Sinistra (Astronomy Department, Hogwarts), points to &amp;lsquo;Atmospheric Unbalancing&amp;rsquo; – a wizarding analogue to the Muggle concept of Climate Change. The culprit? Broomstick emissions, particularly from high-performance models like the Firebolt and the Comet series.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
