<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Developments in Artificial Intelligence on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/developments-in-artificial-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Developments in Artificial Intelligence on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/developments-in-artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automated Aurors: Progress or Peril for the Ministry&#39;s Pensieve Budget?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/opinion/automated-aurors-progress-or-peril-for-the-ministr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/opinion/automated-aurors-progress-or-peril-for-the-ministr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Magic is abuzz, not with excitement for the upcoming Quidditch season (though the Montrose Magpies&amp;rsquo; new Seeker, apparently, is quite the looker), but with the unveiling of a rather… innovative… approach to law enforcement. Minister Shacklebolt, ever the forward-thinking leader (or so he claims after his morning cuppa with his lucky Grindylow&amp;rsquo;s eyeball), has championed the development of what can only be described as &amp;lsquo;Artificial Magical Intelligence,&amp;rsquo; or AMI for those of us who prefer brevity and avoid tongue-tying.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Sorting Socks and Sentient Spells: Are We Conjuring Our Own Doom?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/opinion/self-sorting-socks-and-sentient-spells-are-we-conj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/opinion/self-sorting-socks-and-sentient-spells-are-we-conj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By Bathilda Bagshot (Retired, and Frankly, Terrified)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For centuries, wizards have prided themselves on their ingenuity, their ability to bend reality to their will with a flick of the wand. But are we, in our relentless pursuit of magical innovation, inadvertently creating something&amp;hellip; dangerous? I speak, of course, of the alarming advancements in what I shall term &amp;lsquo;Artificially Enhanced Magic&amp;rsquo; – or, as my neighbour, Mrs. Higgins, calls it, &amp;rsquo;those blasted automatons getting above their station!&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
