<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Climate Change and Extreme Weather Events on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/climate-change-and-extreme-weather-events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Climate Change and Extreme Weather Events on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/climate-change-and-extreme-weather-events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented Weather Woes Plague Quidditch Season: Blame the Boggarts?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/quidditch/unprecedented-weather-woes-plague-quidditch-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/quidditch/unprecedented-weather-woes-plague-quidditch-season/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Quidditch season is barely a fortnight old, and already whispers of doom are circulating faster than a Firebolt on Nitrous Oxide. Forget Rita Skeeter’s scandalous (and entirely fabricated) love triangles, the real drama is in the sky – or rather, what&amp;rsquo;s falling from it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last week&amp;rsquo;s match between the Holyhead Harpies and the Montrose Magpies was suspended in the third quarter when a sudden hailstorm, described by veteran referee Horace Slughorn as &amp;rsquo;larger than Dragon eggs, and twice as unpleasant,&amp;rsquo; bombarded the pitch. Players and spectators alike were forced to seek refuge under hastily erected Protego charms, leading to several amusing (but reportedly painful) incidents involving stray Bludgers ricocheting off said charms.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wonky Weather Wreaks Havoc on Quidditch Pitches!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/quidditch/wonky-weather-wreaks-havoc-on-quidditch-pitches/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/quidditch/wonky-weather-wreaks-havoc-on-quidditch-pitches/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Across the British Isles and beyond, Quidditch enthusiasts are facing an unprecedented challenge: unpredictable and downright dangerous weather patterns. Forget a bit of drizzle during a match; we&amp;rsquo;re talking rogue blizzards in July, spontaneously combusting goalposts, and winds so strong they turn Quaffles into miniature, high-speed Seeking Snitches.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen anything like it!&amp;rdquo; exclaimed Madam Hooch, Headmistress of Flying at Hogwarts. &amp;ldquo;One minute you&amp;rsquo;re demonstrating a simple loop-the-loop, the next you&amp;rsquo;re dodging a flock of flamingos that seem to have Apparated straight from the Sahara – in the middle of Scotland! The brooms are struggling to compensate. Honestly, it&amp;rsquo;s a wonder the students haven&amp;rsquo;t spontaneously developed gills!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
