<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Economic Inflation and Cost of Living Crisis on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/economic-inflation-and-cost-of-living-crisis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Economic Inflation and Cost of Living Crisis on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/economic-inflation-and-cost-of-living-crisis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Are Galleons Gone for Good? A Look at Wizarding Britain&#39;s Crumbling Economy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/features/are-galleons-gone-for-good-a-look-at-wizarding-bri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/features/are-galleons-gone-for-good-a-look-at-wizarding-bri/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By Rita Skeeter (With Quill and Veritaserum&amp;hellip;Mostly)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wizarding Britain is facing a crisis. Forget You-Know-Who – the real Dark Lord lurking in the shadows is Inflation. Yes, dear readers, even we, shielded by Gringotts’ gold reserves (apparently not shielded enough!), are feeling the pinch. The price of a basic cauldron has skyrocketed higher than Neville Longbottom on a Firebolt! And don&amp;rsquo;t even get me started on dragon dung fertiliser; it’s practically rarer than a happy Ministry employee.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knuts and Nifflers: Is the Wizarding World Headed for Galleon-Sized Trouble?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/features/knuts-and-nifflers-is-the-wizarding-world-headed-f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/features/knuts-and-nifflers-is-the-wizarding-world-headed-f/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By Barnaby Broadbent, Financial Felicitations Correspondent&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The price of Pumpkin Pasties has skyrocketed. Gillyweed is practically liquid gold (ironic, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?). And rumour has it, even Cornelius Fudge is tightening his purse strings – though that might just be because he’s finally run out of official Ministry stationery to pilfer. The wizarding world is feeling the pinch, folks. Inflation, that dreaded M-word (no, not Muggle, Monetary!), has reared its ugly head, and our galleons aren&amp;rsquo;t stretching as far as they used to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
