<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Pox Surge Spurs Ministry Emergency Measures!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/dragon-pox-surge-spurs-ministry-emergency-measures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/dragon-pox-surge-spurs-ministry-emergency-measures/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A concerning spike in Dragon Pox cases across Europe and beyond has prompted the Ministry of Magic to declare a Level Three Health Emergency. St. Mungo&amp;rsquo;s Hospital for Magical Maladies and Injuries reports a threefold increase in admissions compared to this time last year, particularly affecting younger witches and wizards who haven&amp;rsquo;t received the full complement of preventative charms. Minister for Magic Kingsley Shacklebolt addressed the Wizengamot this morning, outlining the Ministry&amp;rsquo;s strategy to combat the outbreak. Key initiatives include: a mandatory Pox Protection Protocol, requiring all magical households to administer preventative charms; an accelerated production and distribution of Dragon Pox Potions by Gladrags Wizardwear (renowned for their healing textiles and potions subsidiary); and increased funding for research into more effective and long-lasting immunities, spearheaded by a team of Curse-Breakers and Potioneers led by Professor Neville Longbottom at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erratic Weather and Vanishing Violets: Is Wizarding Climate in Crisis?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/erratic-weather-and-vanishing-violets-is-wizarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/erratic-weather-and-vanishing-violets-is-wizarding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By Barnaby Cuffe, Chief Correspondent&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Magic is facing increasing pressure to address what some are calling a &amp;lsquo;wizarding climate crisis.&amp;rsquo; Reports are flooding in from across the British Isles detailing unsettling magical weather patterns and unusual ecological disruptions. Herbologists are particularly concerned.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;The Venus Flytraps used to enjoy a good, consistent downpour,&amp;rsquo; explained Professor Sprout in an exclusive interview with the Prophet. &amp;lsquo;Now, we have week-long droughts followed by deluges of enchanted rain that corrode the soil. My Mandrakes are simply &lt;em&gt;furious&lt;/em&gt;.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
