<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advances in Medical Technology and Disease Outbreaks on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/advances-in-medical-technology-and-disease-outbreaks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Advances in Medical Technology and Disease Outbreaks on The Hogwarts Hoaxes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/advances-in-medical-technology-and-disease-outbreaks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fluctuating Fortescue: Magical Measles Mutation Spreads Through Wizarding Britain!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/breaking-news/fluctuating-fortescue-magical-measles-mutation-spr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/breaking-news/fluctuating-fortescue-magical-measles-mutation-spr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BREAKING NEWS: St. Mungo&amp;rsquo;s Hospital for Magical Maladies and Injuries is bracing for a surge in cases of &amp;lsquo;Fluctuating Fortescue,&amp;rsquo; a highly contagious (and frankly, rather embarrassing) strain of Magical Measles sweeping across Wizarding Britain. The Ministry of Magic&amp;rsquo;s Department of Magical Health has issued an urgent advisory, urging witches and wizards to immediately consult their Healers if they experience symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms, as described by Healer Smethwyck at St. Mungo&amp;rsquo;s, include: &amp;ldquo;Unpredictable changes in ice cream flavor preferences – one minute you&amp;rsquo;re craving a Knickerbocker Glory, the next it&amp;rsquo;s a Cauldron Cake compulsion! In extreme cases, patients have been observed attempting to transfigure everyday objects into various frozen confections. We also note an increased susceptibility to jinxes involving dairy products.&amp;rdquo; Healer Smethwyck was unfortunately unavailable for further comment as he was last seen wrestling a rogue garden gnome attempting to churn butter with its beard.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
